A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Vice Presidential, 6
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G1460 - 2-3 Dennis Farley, 4-6 Bob Armao, 7-19 Economic/Energy Meeting, 1975 July 18; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1461 - G1464 - The Vice President in Cincinnati, Ohio for Midwest Governor's Conference, 1975 July 22; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1465 - Admiral's House with Dorothy Miller, Navy Secretary Mittendorf, Happy. Presentation of Inaugural Medal, 1975 July 23; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1466 - Admiral's House with Dorothy Miller, Ceremonial Office with Susan Herter, 1975 July 23; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1467 - Senator Kennedy, Mathias and Susan Herter, 1975 July 23; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1468 - G1470 - Press Picnic at Vice President's Foxhall Residence, 1975 July 23; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1472 - Press Party at Foxhall Residence of Vice President, 1975 July 23; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1473 - G1475 - Press Picnic at Vice President's Foxhall Residence, 1975 July 23; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1476 - 3-13 Admiral's House, 14-26 Inaugural Medal Presentation, 27-29 Senator Kennedy, 30-32 Senator Mathias, 1975 July 24; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1477 - Vice President and President, 1975 July 24; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1478 - GRF and Terry O'Donnell, 1975 July 24; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1479 - Vince Albano and David Gravier -National Gallery Opening of Hermitage show, 1975 July 28; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1480 - National Gallery -Opening of Hermitage Show, 1975 July 28; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1481 - G1482 - National Gallery of Art - Preview of the Hermitage Collection, 1975 July 29; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1483 - Golden Gavel Award with Senate pages, Energy Industry meeting, Peter Boaras, 1975 July 29; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1484 - Golden Gavel Awards with Senate pages, 1975 July 29; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1485 - Meeting with Senator Mike Mansfield and Presentation of the Golden Gavel Award, 1975 July 29; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1486 - 4-22 Presentation of Golden Gavel Award, 23-28 Energy Conference, 1975 July 29; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1487 - 3-8 Ambassador Kenneth Rush, 9-12 Nancy Kissinger, 13-17 Robert Seamans and Bill Donaldson, 1975 July 29; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1488 - The Vice President with R. Heath Larry, 1975 July 30; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1489 - 3-4 R. Heath Larry, 5-18 Senator Tower and Senator Stevens, rest is Vice President, 1975 July 30; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1490 - Hooker, Canfield, Senators Tower and Stevens in ceremonial office on Hill, Paul Healy, Meeting with Mithchell, Shafer, Henry Diamond, and General Clark, 1975 July 30; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1491 - Vice President Rockefeller, 1975 July 30; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1492 - Vice President in office with Susan Herter, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1493 - Vice President with Mrs. C. Barrett, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1494 - Staff Meeting - Veneman, Allison, Ronan, Donaldson, Dunham, Meeting - Shafer, Perry Wilson, Warren Anderson, Jack Hanley, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1495 - The Vice President meets with Bill Donaldson, Bill Ronan, Dick Allison, Jack Veneman and Dick Dunham, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1496 - 3-9 Dean Alfange, 10-13 Mrs. C. Barrett, 14-20 The Vice President and Ray Shafer, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1497 - 3-7 Nancy Kissinger, 8-15 Meeting with Donaldson, Ronan, Allison, Veneman and Dunham, 16-20 Dean Alfange, 21-23 Bill Donaldson and Herter, 24-25 Mrs. C. Barrett, 26-35 Meeting with representatives of Union Carbide, 1975 July 31; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1498 - Staff Meeting with Veneman, Wallison, Allison, Shafer, Morrow and Howe, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1499 - Vice President with Jack Veneman, Economic and Energy Meeting, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1500 - Vice President in Roosevelt Room, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1502 - The Vice President with Spof Canfield and Bill Donaldson, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1503 - The Vice President with Jack Veneman and Staff, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1504 - 3-8 Vice President Staff, 9-17 Summer Interns at the Capitol, 18-25 Economic Meeting, 1975 August 1; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1505 - G1507 - The Vice President at Gallaudet College, Washington D.C., 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1509 - Vice President talks to White House interns, 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1510 - Happy with Mrs. Miki leaving Sequoia at Mt. Vernon, 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1511 - Vice President with Ambassador Zahedi and White House interns, 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1512 - Vice President talks to White House interns, 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1513 - Happy with Mrs. Miki of Japan at Blair House, on the Sequoia and at Mt. Vernon, 1975 August 5; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1514 - Happy Rockefeller at Mt. Vernon with Mrs. Miki and her group from Japan, 1975 August 5; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1515 - Happy Rockefeller entertaining Mrs. Miki of Japan on the Sequoia, 1975 August 5; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1516 - The Vice President with the White House interns, 1975 August 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1517 - Vice President with Senator Tower for the Health Productivity Center announcement and paying a courtesy call on Prime Minister Takeo Miki of Japan at Blair House, 1975 August 6; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1518 - Vice President with Senator Tower for the Health Productivity Center announcement, 1975 August 6; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1519 - The Vice President visits the Japanese Embassy, 1975 August 6; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1520 - Vice President at signing ceremony of the Voting Rights Extension Act in the Rose Garden with Thadd Garrett and at the Japanese Embassy with Happy and Prime Minister Takeo Miki, 1975 August 6; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1521 - Vice President at signing ceremony of Voting Rights Extension Act, with Senator Tower in OEOB, and with Prime Minister Takeo Miki of Japan at Blair House, 1975 August 6; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1522 - Vice President Staff John Mulliken -- Deputy Press Secretary, 1975 August 12; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1523 - Vice President Staff - Veneman and Mulliken, 1975 August 12; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1524 - G1525 - Dinner at the White House with the Fords and Rockefellers (not for release), 1975 August 9; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1526 - The Vice President at Seal Harbor, Maine, 1975 August 22; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1527 - Rockefeller meets the press on the dock at his Seal Harbor Residence, 1975 August 22; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1528 - G1531 - Rockefeller hosts a party at his Seal Harbor Residence for Republicans, 1975 August 22; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1532 - Rockefeller meets the press on the dock of his Seal Harbor residence, 1975 August 26; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1533 - Rockefeller meets the press on the dock of his Seal Harbor residence, 1975 August 25; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1534 - Rockefeller hosts a party at his Seal Harbor residence for Republicans, 1975 August 25; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1535 - Vice President Rockefeller hosts a party for Republicans at his Seal Harbor, Maine residence, 1975 August 25; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1536 - Copy of Vice Presidential seal?, 1975 August 25; Color (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1537 - Vice President with Susan Herter, Bill Donaldson and Jim Cannon, 1975 August 26; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1538 - Vice President with Susan Herter, Jim Cannon, Bill Donaldson, and the President, 1975 August 26; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1539 - Mobile, Alabama, 1975 August 27; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1540 - G1543 - Columbia, South Carolina, 1975 August 27; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1545 - Mobile, Alabama, 1975 August 26; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1546 - 3-13 Bill Donaldson and Energy Meeting, 14-28 Mobile, Alabama, 1975 August 26; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1547 - G1550 - Mobile, Alabama, 1975 August 26; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 15, Volume 8)
    - G1551 - G1552 - Mobile, Alabama, 1975 August 26; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1553 - Donaldson and Cannon; GRF, 1975 September 2; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1554 - Productivity Committee; Sasha Norkin; Donaldson and Cannon, 1975 September 2; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1555 - Sen. Cotton (NH) swearing in; Capitol Hill office, 1975 September 3; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1556 - Sen. Cotton (NH) swearing in; Capitol Hill office; energy luncheon, EOB office, 1975 September 3; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1557 - G1560 - Rochester, NY, 1975 September 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1561 - Rochester, NY, 1975 September 5; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1562 - G1567 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 5; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1568 - Kissinger and Cannon; Sam Aldrich; science leaders, 1975 September 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1569 - Paulo and Mauro Leone; bi-partisan meeting; Sam Aldrich; science leaders, 1975 September 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1570 - G1573 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 5; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1574 - Gerald Zarnow and Michael Harrigan; Bob Georgina; Major Williams award, 1975 September 8; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1575 - Major Williams award; Naval Observatory, 1975 September 8; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1576 - Happy Rockefeller, 1975 September 10; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1577 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 8; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1578 - Jaime Benitez; Sens. Baker (TN) and Muskie (ME); Water Quality Commission; house warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 9; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1579 - G1582 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 9; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1583 - Painting for Vice President, 1975 September 10; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1584 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 9; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1585 - Capitol Hill Club reception, 1975 September 11; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1586 - Savings bond award ceremony, 1975 September 10; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1587 - G1588 - Enid, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1589 - Dallas, Texas; Little Rock, Arkansas; Norman, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1590 - Norman, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1591 - G1596 - World of Jefferson and Franklin exhibit, London, England, 1975 September 13; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1597 - Norman, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1598 - Norman, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1599 - Norman, Oklahoma, 1975 September 13; Color (Box 4, Folder 16, Volume 8)
    - G1600 - Life" magazine bicentennial edition; George Bush; Lowell Thomas, Jr., 34-37 Dallas, Texas, 1975 September 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1601 - G1602 - Dallas, Texas, 1975 September 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1603 - Life" magazine bicentennial edition; Frances Knight, Dallas, Texas, 1975 September 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1604 - Dallas, Texas, 1975 September 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1605 - G1608 - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1975 September 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1609 - Old Vice Presidential flag (1936), 1975 September 17; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1612 - Present Vice Presidential flag (1948), 1975 September 17; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1614 - National Archives- reading is fundamental, 1975 September 17; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1615 - National Archives- reading is fundamental, 1975 September 17; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1616 - Margaret Thatcher dinner, British embassy, 1975 September 18; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1617 - Senate Staff Club annual picnic, 1975 September 18; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1618 - National Archives- reading is fundamental; National Medal of Science; Charles Schlaifer, 1975 September 17; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1619 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1620 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1621 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 22; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1622 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 22; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1623 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1624 - Inter-agency meeting; Mike Waldman; Hooker and Canfield; Rep. Biester (PA) and Bucks County Historical Tourist Agency; Rep. McClory (IL), 1975 September 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1625 - Dr. Elson, Senate Chaplain; Canfield and Hooker, 1975 September 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1626 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1627 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 23; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1628 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 24; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1629 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 24; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1630 - Cannon and Sen. Cook; NAR; Bicentennial presentation Public Occurrences"; NBC film crew; Justice Hope; Lloyd Free ", 1975 September 24; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1631 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 September 24; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1632 - Sen. Cook (KY); bicentennial presentation Public Occurrences"; Rita Hauser ", 1975 September 24; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1633 - Columbian President Lopez Michelson, Blair House, 1975 September 25; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1634 - G1637 - Republican Party chairman, Pocantico Hills, 1975 September 26; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1638 - Republican Party Chairman, Pocantico Hills, 1975 September 26; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1639 - Leon Higginbotham; Smithsonian Board of Regents, 1975 September 30; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1640 - Federal City Council; Sen. Mansfield (MT); Frank Fitzsimmons and Murray Miller; George Klein; Russ Peterson; Smithsonian Board of Regents, 1975 September 30; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1641 - Federal City Council; Hugh Morrow's birthday party; Frank Fitzsimmons and Murray Miller; Smithsonian Board of Regents, 1975 September 30; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1642 - Bobby Depropero and family, 1975 October 1; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1643 - Black Caucus meeting; Evans and Novak political forum, 1975 October 1; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1644 - G1648 - Emperor Hirohito at Pocantico Hills, 1975 October 5; Color (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1649 - G1652 - Portland, Oregon, 1975 October 3; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 17, Volume 9)
    - G1653 - Marcus Nadjari; National Energy Project conference, 1975 October 2; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1654 - Portland, Oregon, 1975 October 3; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1655 - G1658 - King's Mountain Bicentennial ceremony, 1975 October 7; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1659 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1660 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1662 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1663 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1664 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1665 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 6; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1666 - Energy executives meeting; Viscount Bothelo; Water Quality Commission, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1667 - Visitors to capitol; Mr. and Mrs. Peter McDonald; Water Quality Commission, 1975 October 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1668 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 8; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1669 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 8; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1670 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 8; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1671 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 8; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1672 - House warming, Naval Observatory, 1975 October 8; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1673 - house warming; Bo Callaway; drug abuse task force; E. I. A. press briefing, 1975 October 10; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1674 - Bo Callaway; drug abuse task force; Lt. Gen. James Allen; Privacy Commission, 1975 October 10; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1675 - Columbus Day dinner, New York, 1975 October 11; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1676 - Launching of the Dwight D. Eisenhower Nuclear Aircraft Carrier, Newport News, Virginia, 1975 October 11; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1677 - King of Norway; USS Eisenhower launching, 1975 October 11; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1678 - USS Eisenhower launching; Columbus Day dinner, New York, 1975 October 11; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1679 - G1680 - Lord Mountbatten at Pocantico Hills, 1975 October 11; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1681 - Sinai Agreement signing; Lord Mountbatten, 1975 October 10; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1682 - Sinai Agreement signing, 1975 October 10; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1683 - Roanoke, Virginia, 1975 October 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1684 - Roanoke, Virginia, 1975 October 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1685 - G1687 - Columbus, Ohio, 1975 October 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1688 - Columbus, Ohio, 1975 October 15; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1689 - Charleston, West Virginia, 1975 October 16; Color (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1690 - Columbus, Ohio; Charleston, West Virginia, 1975 October 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1691 - Charleston, West Virginia, 1975 October 16; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1692 - Society of American Travel Writers; Ken Spencer, 1975 October 17; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1693 - Dick Dunham swearing in, 1975 October 20; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1694 - Dick Dunham swearing in, 1975 October 20; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1695 - G1699 - Denver, Colorado, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 18, Volume 9)
    - G1700 - Rep. Brown (OH); gifts from Hirohito, 1975 October 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1701 - Rep. Brown (OH); Rep. Hagedorn (MN) and town and township representatives, 1975 October 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1702 - Martin Agronsky and Paul Duke; congressional wives lunch, 1975 October 22; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1703 - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1704 - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1705 - G1707 - Decatur, Illinois, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1708 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1709 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1710 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1711 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1712 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1713 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1714 - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1975 October 23; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1715 - Anwar Sadat at Blair House, 1975 October 27; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1716 - Anwar Sadat at Blair House, 1975 October 27; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1717 - Anwar Sadat in Chicago; Anwar Sadat aboard Air Force One; Anwar Sadat in Houston, 1975 October 31; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1718 - G1721 - Anwar Sadat in Houston, 1975 October 31; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1722 - G1725 - Anwar Sadat at Pocantico Hills, 1975 October 31; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1726 - G1727 - Hebrew College honorary degree, New York, 1975 October 30; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1728 - G1731 - Tampa, Florida, 1975 October 30; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1732 - Tampa, Florida, 1975 October 30; Color (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1733 - Henry Kissinger, 1975 November 3; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1734 - Roger Hooker portraits, 1975 November 5; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)